Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - Report on the Resident Student Survey [binder] (2 of 3), 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Report on the Resident Student Survey [binder] (3 of 3), 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Res-Life, 1996; UA042.001.068.00016 (Box 68)
    - Residential Life RA, Proctor Evaluations, 1996; UA042.001.068.00016.00001
    - Resident Student Survey, 1996; UA042.001.068.00016.00002
  - Res. Life Proctor Evaluation, 1995; UA042.001.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations RAs and Proctors [binder] (1 of 4), 1997; UA042.001.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations RAs and Proctors [binder] (2 of 4), 1997; UA042.001.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations RAs and Proctors [binder] (3 of 4), 1997; UA042.001.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations RAs and Proctors [binder] (4 of 4), 1997; UA042.001.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations Resident Student Survey [binder] (1 of 4), 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.068.00022 (Box 68)
    - Res Life Student Survey, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.068.00022.00001
  - Resident Life Evaluations Resident Student Survey [binder] (2 of 4), 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations Resident Student Survey [binder] (3 of 4), 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Resident Life Evaluations Resident Student Survey [binder] (4 of 4), 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.068.00025 (Box 68)
  - Residence Life Duty Team Police Liaison Program, 1998; UA042.001.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Resident Student Survey, 1997; UA042.001.069.00002 (Box 69)
    - Resident Life Student Survey, 1997; UA042.001.069.00002.00001
  - Resident Student Survey, 1990; UA042.001.069.00003 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (1 of 4), 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.069.00004 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (2 of 4), 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.069.00005 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (3 of 4), 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.069.00006 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (4 of 4), 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.069.00007 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (1 of 4), 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.069.00008 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (2 of 4), 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.069.00009 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (3 of 4), 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.069.00010 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (4 of 4), 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.069.00011 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (1 of 3), 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.069.00012 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (2 of 3), 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.069.00013 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey [binder] (3 of 3), 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.069.00014 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey DATA, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.069.00015 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey Original Instrument, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.069.00016 (Box 69)
  - Resident Student Survey, 1989; UA042.001.069.00017 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Data [binder] (1 of 4), 2000; UA042.001.069.00018 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Data [binder] (2 of 4), 2000; UA042.001.069.00019 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Data [binder] (3 of 4), 2000; UA042.001.069.00020 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Data [binder] (4 of 4), 2000; UA042.001.069.00021 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Graphs [binder] (1 of 3), 2001; UA042.001.069.00022 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Graphs [binder] (2 of 3), 2001; UA042.001.069.00023 (Box 69)
  - Residential Life Survey - Report, Previews, Graphs [binder] (3 of 3), 2001; UA042.001.069.00024 (Box 69)
  - Retention '86-'95, 1999; UA042.001.069.00025 (Box 69)
  - Retention - 1995 Cohort - Class of 1999, 2002; UA042.001.069.00026 (Box 69)
  - Retention - Class of 1997 - 1993 Cohort, 2000; UA042.001.069.00027 (Box 69)
  - Retention - 1992 Cohort - Class of 1996, 1999; UA042.001.069.00028 (Box 69)
  - Retention - 1991 Cohort - Class of 1995, 1998; UA042.001.069.00029 (Box 69)
  - Retention - Class of 1994 - 1990 Cohort, UA042.001.069.00030 (Box 69)
  - Retention - Class of 1993 - 1989 Cohort, 1996; UA042.001.069.00031 (Box 69)
  - Retention - Class of 1992 - 1988 Cohort, 1995; UA042.001.069.00032 (Box 69)
  - Retention - Class of 1991 - 1987 Cohort, 1993; UA042.001.069.00033 (Box 69)
    - Retention Study Class of 1991, 1993; UA042.001.069.00033.00001
  - Retention, Classes '90 - '94 for Meeting of Black Faculty & Admin., 1995; UA042.001.069.00034 (Box 69)
  - Retention - International 1990 Cohort, 1997; UA042.001.069.00035 (Box 69)
  - Retention and Graduation Rate Info NE Bd of Higher Education, 1995; UA042.001.069.00036 (Box 69)
  - Retention/Graduation Data - Sharing, 1998; UA042.001.070.00001 (Box 70)
  - Retention Study - Class of 1990 - 1986 Cohort, 1992; UA042.001.070.00002 (Box 70)
  - Retention Study Class of 1991 Minority-Focused, 1994; UA042.001.070.00003 (Box 70)
  - Retention Survey, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.070.00004
  - Retirement: Misc Surveys, 1973 -- 1987; UA042.001.070.00005 (Box 70)
  - Sackler Admission Inq., 1990; UA042.001.070.00006 (Box 70)
  - SCUP, 1989; UA042.001.070.00007 (Box 70)
  - Security Survey of 28 Sawyer, 1991; UA042.001.070.00008 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Report, 1993; UA042.001.070.00009 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey [binder], 1995; UA042.001.070.00010 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey, 1997 -- 2003; UA042.001.070.00011 (Box 70)
    - Senior Survey, 1997 -- 2003; UA042.001.070.00011.00001
  - Senior Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.070.00012 (Box 70)
    - Jobs and Graduate School Plans, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.070.00012.00001
    - Senior Survey Data Files, 1998; UA042.001.070.00012.00002
  - Senior Survey Nominations, 1995; UA042.001.070.00013 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Nominations, 1998; UA042.001.070.00014 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey 5 Year Comparisons, 1988 -- 1992; UA042.001.070.00015 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey 5 Year Stuff, 1988 -- 1992; UA042.001.070.00016 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Codebook [binder] (1 of 2), 1996; UA042.001.070.00017 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Codebook [binder] (2 of 2), 1996; UA042.001.070.00018 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Compara. Data (HEDS), 1991; UA042.001.070.00019 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey - Comparisons, 1996; UA042.001.070.00020 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Alphabetical Order) [binder] (1 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00021 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Alphabetical Order) [binder] (2 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00022 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Alphabetical Order) [binder] (3 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00023 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Numerical Order) [binder] (1 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00024 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Numerical Order) [binder] (2 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00025 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Course Listings by Department (Numerical Order) [binder] (3 of 3), 1996; UA042.001.070.00026 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Department Profiles, 1997; UA042.001.070.00027 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Historical Data of Natural Sciences, 1992; UA042.001.070.00028 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Importance/Satisfaction, 1995; UA042.001.070.00029 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey Inquire from Pearl Robinson, 1999; UA042.001.070.00030 (Box 70)
  - Senior Survey "Major by Race Data -- Class of 1992", 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.070.00031 (Box 70)
  - Senior Surveys, 1997; UA042.001.070.00032 (Box 70)
  - Senior Surveys, 1998; UA042.001.070.00033 (Box 70)
  - Senior Surveys [binder] (1 of 3), 1985 -- 1996; UA042.001.070.00034 (Box 70)
  - Senior Surveys [binder] (2 of 3), 1985 -- 1996; UA042.001.070.00035 (Box 70)
  - Senior Surveys [binder] (3 of 3), 1985 -- 1996; UA042.001.070.00036 (Box 70)
  - Skills, 1996; UA042.001.070.00037 (Box 70)
  - SPRE, 1994; UA042.001.070.00038 (Box 70)
  - The State of the Art In Student Choice Research, 1984; UA042.001.070.00039 (Box 70)
  - Surveys, 1997 -- 2002; UA042.001.071.00001 (Box 71)
  - Time to Degree, 1997; UA042.001.071.00002 (Box 71)
  - Tufts Faculty Salary Analysis [binder], 1981; UA042.001.071.00003 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Alumni Survey Class of 1982 [binder], 1993; UA042.001.071.00004 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report, 1998; UA042.001.071.00005 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report (1 of 2), 1996; UA042.001.071.00006 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report (2 of 2), 1996; UA042.001.071.00007 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report [binder](1 of 3), 1997; UA042.001.071.00008 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report [binder](2 of 3), 1997; UA042.001.071.00009 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Inquiry Survey Report [binder](3 of 3), 1997; UA042.001.071.00010 (Box 71)
  - AAUP Faculty Salary Data, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - A Survey of APSIA Schools on Admissions, Students, and Student Charges - Final Report, 1988; UA042.001.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - CGS/GRE Survey of Graduate Enrollments, 1989; UA042.001.072.00003 (Box 72)
  - Committee on Fraternities and Sororities Report, 1992; UA042.001.072.00004 (Box 72)
  - Comparative Fundraising Achievement, 1991; UA042.001.072.00005 (Box 72)
  - Computer Support Group FSP Questionnaire, 1998; UA042.001.072.00006 (Box 72)
    - Computer End User Survey FSP, 1998; UA042.001.072.00006.00001
  - Directions for the 1990's: A proposed Strategic Plan for The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy - Draft, 1989; UA042.001.072.00007 (Box 72)
  - Fletcher Admissions - Non-Matriculating, 1997; UA042.001.072.00008 (Box 72)
    - Fletcher Admissions Non-Matriculating Survey, 1997; UA042.001.072.00008.00001
  - Fletcher School Admission, 1999; UA042.001.072.00009 (Box 72)
    - Fletcher Non-Matriculating, 1999; UA042.001.072.00009.00001
    - Fletcher Matriculating, 1999; UA042.001.072.00009.00002
  - Fletcher Alumni Questionnaire, 1993; UA042.001.072.00010 (Box 72)
  - Fund-Raising Costs and Staffing: A comparison of Ten Private Universities, 1985; UA042.001.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - Fund-Raising in U.S. Colleges and Univerities: The Fifty Best Performances, 1979-80 Through 1985-1986, 1988; UA042.001.072.00012 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Codebook, 1995; UA042.001.072.00013 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1988; UA042.001.072.00014 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1989; UA042.001.072.00015 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey Frequencies and Valid Percents, 1990; UA042.001.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1991; UA042.001.072.00017 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1994; UA042.001.072.00018 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1995; UA042.001.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - Graduate Student Survey, 1996; UA042.001.072.00020 (Box 72)
  - GSAS 3 Year Trends (means), 1997 -- 2000; UA042.001.072.00021 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Exiting Survey, 1997; UA042.001.072.00022 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Exit Survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.072.00023 (Box 72)
    - New Graduate Survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.072.00023.00001
  - GSAS Exiting Survey, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.072.00024 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Exiting Survey Comments, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.072.00025 (Box 72)
  - Ivy League Questionnaire - Influences on the Career Choices of High Achieving Minority Group College Students, 1996; UA042.001.072.00026 (Box 72)
    - Ivy League Questionnaire, 1996; UA042.001.072.00026.00001
  - Library User Survey, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.072.00027 (Box 72)
  - Most Similar College Data, 1995; UA042.001.072.00028 (Box 72)
  - Professors & Course Ratings, 1998; UA042.001.072.00029 (Box 72)
  - The Fletcher School Admissions Questionnaire, 1998; UA042.001.072.00030 (Box 72)
    - Fletcher Admissions, 1998; UA042.001.072.00030.00001
  - The Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire (Spring), 1999; UA042.001.072.00031 (Box 72)
    - Fletcher Course Evaluations Spring, 1999; UA042.001.072.00031.00001
  - The Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire (Fall), 1999; UA042.001.072.00032 (Box 72)
    - Fletcher Course Evaluations Fall, 1999; UA042.001.072.00032.00001
  - Tisch Library Faculty Survey, 1998; UA042.001.072.00033 (Box 72)
  - Tisch Library Student Survey, 1998; UA042.001.072.00034 (Box 72)
  - Tisch Library Survey (Faculty/Student), 1997; UA042.001.072.00035 (Box 72)
    - Tisch Library Survey, 1997; UA042.001.072.00035.00001
  - Tisch Library Website Focus Groups Report, 1999; UA042.001.072.00036 (Box 72)
  - Tisch Web Usability Survey, 1999; UA042.001.072.00037 (Box 72)
  - Tufts University Arts and Sciences Library Survey, 1993; UA042.001.072.00038 (Box 72)
  - Tufts University Arts and Sciences Library Spring User Survey, 1994; UA042.001.072.00039 (Box 72)
    - Library Survey Backup Disc, 1994; UA042.001.072.00039.00001
    - Library User Survey, 1994; UA042.001.072.00039.00002
    - Library User Survey Docs, 1994; UA042.001.072.00039.00003
    - Library Spring User Study, 1994; UA042.001.072.00039.00004
  - Surveys and reports, 1982 -- 2005; UA042.001.073 (Box 73)
    Campus master plans, circa 1986; Trustees Retreat workbook, 1993; Accepted Applicant Studies, 1993, 1994, 1996; Survey of Secondary School Guidance and College Counselors, 2004; Committee on Strategic Planning for the School of Arts and Sciences, 2004-2005.
- Additional accessions, 1995 -- 2001; UA042.002
  - Advising CDs, 1995 -- 1998; UA042-048
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - 2006-03 continued, 2001; UA042-053 (Box data_value_missing_0fcdd6ebb4028d7fd8df7a48c2c011c8, Box 1)
  - 2006-2 continued and 2006-3, 2001; UA042-054 (Box data_value_missing_5fc291088f914de1e96e9b3322cd4d13, Box 2)
  - Unprocessed digital media, 1988 -- 1996; UA042-073 (Box data_value_missing_fbf4dd39c66d9ea10d78ba01609e3d63, Box 3)
    Open for research.
    This box contains 19 unprocessed 5.25" floppy discs from the Office of Institutional Research.